ZHANG AN

Senior Full Stack Developer

**** +852 8192 6568

@ live:.cid.c7356d23b1a76148

- @ shanehogsett701@gmail.com
- HongKong, China



EXPERIENCE

Asp.net developer

Halian UAE

= 04/2017 - 02/2018

- Developed SelfMIE project using WebRTC, ASP.net, C# and FaceRecog technology
- · Developed MHM project CRM systems using ASP.net.
- Developed HouseVue project using Laravel and Vue.js.

FullStack developer

PROOFS Switzerland

= 03/2018 - 07/2018

- · Developed CRM systems using Figma, React and Node.js.
- Integrated GIS pages using google map API, OpenLayers, ArcGIS and PostGIS
- Delivered eCommerce sites using React, mongoDB, payment APIs.
- · Integrated Web Admin Panel using React and AWS EC2.

Senior Game Developer

Wizcorp Inc, Chuo-ku Tokyo

= 08/2018 - 12/2019

- Developed real-time strategy online game called 'AgeofKingdom' using Unity and PHP.
- Developed multiplayer online battle game similar like 'Brawl Stars' using Unity and Pomelo.
- Designed and developed simple muti-player racing game by Unreal Engine4.
- Designed and developed simple muti-player racing game by Unreal Engine4.
- Designed and developed simple muti-player racing game by Unreal Engine4.

Lead Solidity | Web3 | React Devel

Ratio Finance United states

= 01/2020 - 09/2020

- Developed Vesting & Staking contract using ERC20.
- · Connect Backend and Frontend using Web3.

Senior Solidity | React Developer

ThimbleGang Spain

iii 10/2020 - 07/2021

- · Project similar with CryptoZombie.
- Built NFT marketplace using solidity, web3, React on Ethereum, BSC, polygon with Truffle.
- Developed ERC721, ERC20, ERC1155 smart contracts with solidity.
- Integrated Web3, React, Node and AWS.

Senior React(TypeScript) Developer

Hubble Axiom United Kingdom

ii 10/2021 - 11/2022

- · Developed Rust Smart Contract.
- Developed UI template and Frontend using Figma, React(Javascript, Typescript).

SUMMARY

I am a Senior Software Engineer who has specialized in Full-Stack development especially with React and NodeJs, Angular, Vue and Laravel, Shopify, Symfony so on. I have over 8 years of experience in Web & Mobile Front-end and Back-end using React and Node.

I have developed several applications in various kind of industries including ecommerce, health care, real estate, gaming, web3 and so on.

Equipped with a record of success in consistently identifying and providing the technological needs of companies through ingenious innovation.

Built and maintained strategic relationships with potential investors and business partners and brainstormed new ideas.

SKILLS

Languages - Java, JavaScript, C++, Dart

Frameworks - Vue.JS, Angular.JS,

React.JS, Next.js, Nuxt.js, Laravel,

Codelgniter, Flask, Django

Flutter, React Native, Java, Kotlin

RDBMS - PostgreSQL, MySQL, MariaDB

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

Hong Kong College of Technology

= 08/2011 - 09/2015

LANGUAGES

EnglishProficient



Chinese

Native

